<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Miscellaneous on ResInsight</title>
    <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Miscellaneous on ResInsight</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Preferences</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/preferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/preferences/</guid>
      <description>In this section the different settings that controls the default behavior of ResInsight is described. These settings can be controlled using the Preference dialog available from the Edit -&amp;gt; Preferences menu.
When changing the preferences, any default color, font or Z-scale Factor that has not been changed by the user in the various views, will be applied immediately. If the user has changed font sizes in specific plots or annotations from the default value, ResInsight will ask if the user wants the new defaults applied to all existing views and plots even where custom settings have been set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project File and Caching</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/projectfile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/projectfile/</guid>
      <description>The Project File ResInsight stores all views and settings in a Project File with the extension *.rsp to easily continue work in a subsequent session. This file only contains references to the real data files, and does not in any way copy the data itself. Data files generated by ResInsight are also referenced by the Project File.
The *.rsp file is an XML file, and can be edited by any text editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory Management</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/memorymanagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/memorymanagement/</guid>
      <description>ResInsight can require a considerable amount of memory to hold all the grids and necessary result variables. If the requirements starts approaching the available physical memory on the workstation, ResInsight may become unstable and crash, as the operating system starts freeing memory to avoid system failure. To help alleviate this, ResInsight has some built-in memory management tools.
Memory Indicator The tools are available from the memory indicator in the bottom right corner of the main 3D window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/keyboardshortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/keyboardshortcuts/</guid>
      <description>ResInsight supports a selection of Keyboard Shortcuts for convenience. These include Delete for removing deletable items from the project tree, Ctrl-Alt-A for Zoom All and Ctrl-Alt-S/N/W/E/D/U for changing the camera view to South, North, West, East, Down and Up respectively.
Other available keyboard shortcuts are
 Ctrl-Shift-P for opening up the plot window when you are in the 3d View Ctrl-Shift-3 for opening up the 3d View while you are in the Plot Window Ctrl-X for Cut and Ctrl-V for Paste of project tree items where this functionality is available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regression Test System</title>
      <link>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/regressiontestsystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://opm.github.io/ResInsight-UserDocumentation/misc/regressiontestsystem/</guid>
      <description>A regression tool for QA is build into ResInsight. This tool will do the following:
 Scan a directory for sub directories containing a RegressionTest.rsp files. Each found project file will be opened, and all views in this project will be exported as snapshot images to file. When snapshot images from all projects are completed, difference images based on generated and QA-approved images are computed. Based on these three sets of images, an HTML report is created and automatically displayed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>