<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plot Main Window on ResInsight</title>
    <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Plot Main Window on ResInsight</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://resinsight.org/plot-window/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary Plots</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summaryplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summaryplots/</guid>
      <description>A Summary Plot is a window displaying a graph in the main area of the Plot Main Window. As described below, a Summary Plot can contain Summary Curves, Grid time history curves, and pasted ascii curves.
A new Summary Plot can be created by using the right-click menu of Summary Plots in the Plot Project Tree and activate Open Summary Plot Editor or New Summary Plot.
If you have many open plots, it can be useful to collapse all other plots by activating Collapse Other Plots from right-click menu of a plot in the Plot Project Tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary Plot Source Stepping</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summarysourcestepping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summarysourcestepping/</guid>
      <description>Summary Plot Source Stepping Summary Source Stepping is a function which enables the user to swiftly step through multiple vectors. The functionality applies both to single summary curves and ensemble curve sets.
The functionality is available from both the toolbar and the Summary Curves property editor under a Summary Plot item in the Main Plot Window Project Tree.
The toolbar allows use of vector filters in addition to source stepping:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary Plot Editor</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summaryploteditor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summaryploteditor/</guid>
      <description>The plot editor is a separate ResInsight dialog window where the user can select which vectors to display in a summary plot. It is also possible to edit an existing plot in this editor.
The upper part of the editor contains editors for selecting which vectors/summaries to display in the plot. The number of fields vary from 3 to 6 depending on the Summary Type currently highlighted.
In this context highlighted means the marked item with a different background color, while selected means an item or items that have a ticked check box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary Cross Plot</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summarycrossplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summarycrossplots/</guid>
      <description>A Summary Cross Plot is a window displaying a graph in the main area of the Plot Main Window. It is very similar to an ordinary Summary Plot, but there are some differences:
 Summary Cross Plot displays one vector against another vector, not one vector against time. Not possible to paste Excel/CSV data to a summary cross plot. Summary cross plots have no Plot Editor.  The only way to create a new Summary Cross Plot, is to select the right-click command New Summary Cross Plot on the Plot Main Window -&amp;gt; Project Tree -&amp;gt; Summary Cross Plots item.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary Plot Template</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summaryplottemplate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/summaryplottemplate/</guid>
      <description>Template creation A summary plot template is defined by a number of curves with preset appearance and vector names. The parameters that are selected or varied by the user are:
 case(s) item(s), i.e. well(s), group(s), region(s)  Having tailored a plot setup, the user can save the setup as a template via the right-click command Save As Plot Template, c.f. figure above. It is also possible to select a summary plot in the Plot Project Tree and use the right-click menu to save a template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi Plots</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/multiplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/multiplots/</guid>
      <description>A Multi Plot allows the user to combine multiple plots in a grid layout. Plots from different types can be combined. This plot type is tailored for export to PDF.
Multi Plot Usage A new Multi Plot can be created by selecting a set of plots and from the right-click menu select Create Multi Plot from Selected Plots
The currenly supported types of plots to be part of a Multi Plot are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble Plotting</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/ensembleplotting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/ensembleplotting/</guid>
      <description>An ensemble is a group of cases that are tightly coupled, only a set of ensemble input parameters differ between cases. This makes it relevant to perform calculations and statistics analysis on ensembles.
Import There are several ways to import an ensemble:
 Use menu option File-&amp;gt;Import-&amp;gt;Summary Cases-&amp;gt;Import Ensemble Use menu option File-&amp;gt;Import-&amp;gt;Summary Cases-&amp;gt;Import Summary Case group and then convert the group to an ensemble Import a number of summary cases, move them into a group and then convert the group to an ensemble  During import of a summary case, ResInsight tries to find an associated parameters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analysis Plots</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/analysisplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/analysisplots/</guid>
      <description>Analysis Plots are bar charts used to compare summary data at specific timesteps across Ensembles and Summary Cases.
Creating an Analysis Plot The most convenient way to create an Analysis Plot at a given time step is often to right-click an Ensemble Plot and invoke New Analysis Plot as shown below.
Alternatively, Analysis Plots can be created by right-clicking the Analysis Plots item in Plot Project Tree.
Having created an Analysis Plot, subitems Value Axis and Plot Data Filters emerges in Plot Project Tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Correlation Plots</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/correlationplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/correlationplots/</guid>
      <description>Correlation Plots are plots used to visualize correlations between ensemble parameters and summary result vectors. Several visualizations can be created, including tornado plots, correlation matrices, and cross plots.
Creating a Correlation Plot The most convenient way to create a Correlation Plot at a given time step is often to right-click an Ensemble Plot and invoke the submenu shown below.
Alternatively, Correlation Plots can be created by right-clicking the Correlation Plots item in Plot Project Tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curve Calculator</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/curvecalculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/curvecalculator/</guid>
      <description>The summary curve calculator is a tool to do relative simple vector calculations on a set of curves. The created curves can be stored for later use in the project.
The calculator can be run by pressing the calculator icon in the menu bar, or by right-clicking on either a summary case or the summary plot collection.
Calculation Settings To make a new calculated curve, click on New Calculation. This will add a new calculation to Calculated Summaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well Log Plots</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/welllogsandplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/welllogsandplots/</guid>
      <description>ResInsight can display well logs by extracting data from a simulation model along a well trajectory and from imported LAS-files. Extracted simulation data can be exported to LAS-files for further processing.
Well Log Plots Well log plots can be created in several ways:
 Right-click a well path or a simulation well in the 3D-view and select New Well Log Extraction Curve.
A new plot with a single Track and Curve is created matching active case and selected Well trajectory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well Bore Stability Plots</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/wellborestabilityplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/wellborestabilityplots/</guid>
      <description>ResInsight can create Well Bore Stability plots for Geomechanical cases. These plots are specialized Well Log Plots to visualize Formations, Well Measurements, Well Path Attributes as well as a set of well path derived curves in different tracks.
In the figure above, the first track contains Formations and an indication of sea level.
   Sea Level Formations          The second track contains a visualisation of the well, with well attributes of Casing Design as well Completions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RFT Plot</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/rftplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/rftplot/</guid>
      <description>An RFT (Repeated Formation Tester) plot is a special well plot for comparing observed formation pressure and simulated formation pressure. The curves are plotted as pressure against true vertical depth (TVD) or measured depth (MD). Simulated pressure data is retrieved directly from the grid model or from the corresponding (*.rft) files, while observed pressure data are loaded from well log files (*.las).
Create New RFT Plot There are several ways to create new RFT Plots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble RFT Plot</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/ensemblerftplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/ensemblerftplot/</guid>
      <description>ResInsight allows the user to create a ensemble RFT plot similar to summary ensemble plots. The functionality also computes statistics, e.g. P10, P90, and mean. When possible, ResInsight avoids loading the grid when reading ensemble RFT data.
Create New Ensemble RFT Plot When a summary ensemble has been imported, observed FMU data can be imported via right-clicking Observed Data in the Plot Project Tree, and selecting Import Observed FMU Data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PLT Plot</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/pltplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/pltplot/</guid>
      <description>A PLT (Production Log Tool) plot is a special well plot for comparing observed production (well flow rates) and simulated production. The curves are plotted as production against measured depth (MD). Simulated production data is retrieved directly from the grid model or from the corresponding (*.rft) files, while observed production data are loaded from well log files (*.las).
Create New PLT Plot There are several ways to create new PLT Plots</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flow Diagnostics Plots</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/flowdiagnosticsplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/flowdiagnosticsplots/</guid>
      <description>Flow Diagnostics Plots can be used to view well allocation, well inflow rates, cumulative saturation along time of flight and flow characteristics.
They are managed from the folder Flow Diagnostics Plots located in Plot Project Tree in the Plot Main Window.
This folder contains a default Flow Characteristics Plot and Well Allocation Plot. In addition, two folders with stored well allocation and flow characteristics plots will show up if there are any of those in the model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grid Cross Plots</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/gridcrossplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/gridcrossplots/</guid>
      <description>ResInsight supports the creation of scatter / cross plots of two Eclipse results against each other, with each cell in the grid representing one data point in the plot. The data points can be grouped by a third result, by time step or by Formations. giving a separate color and label for each group. The above example shows a classic Porosity vs Permeability plot, grouped by formations, showing different trends for each formation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturation Pressure Plots</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/saturationpressureplots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/plot-window/saturationpressureplots/</guid>
      <description>A Saturation Pressure Plot a plot displaying bubble and dew point pressures, together with initial pressure in model, versus depth. Fluid contacts (GOC and/or OWC) are displayed as annotation lines in the generated plots. One Saturation Pressure Plot is created for each equilibrium region.
To be able to create these plots, output of saturation pressures need to be specified in the SOLUTION section of the Eclipse &amp;ldquo;.DATA&amp;rdquo; file.
To create these plots, right click on the view in the Property Editor, and select Create Saturation Pressure Plots.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>