<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release Notes :: ResInsight</title>
    <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/index.html</link>
    <description></description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2024.12</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2024_12/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2024_12/index.html</guid>
      <description>Grid Import Performance ResInsight now offers the option to import geometry exclusively for active cells. This feature is particularly beneficial for large grids where active cells constitute only a small fraction of the total, significantly reducing memory usage. This optimization ensures efficient handling of large models while maintaining full functionality for active cells.&#xA;Preferences&#xA;Performance Hints&#xA;Quick Access View</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2024.09</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2024_09/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2024_09/index.html</guid>
      <description>Cloud Services ResInsight has now support for import of data from two cloud services, ensemble summary data from SUMO and well path geometry from OSDU.&#xA;Cloud Services&#xA;Ensemble Grid Case An ensemble of grid cases can be imported into a grid case ensemble. Creating a view in this ensemble will allow the user to quickly switch between realizations using a drop down menu.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2024.03</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2024_03/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2024_03/index.html</guid>
      <description>Grid Calculations Grid Property Calculations perform better for multiple (large) grid models&#xA;Polygons Polygons are now available as project objects, and a can be displayed in 3D views. A polygon can also be used to define an intersection and polygon cell filters. Polygons can be imported from a file, or created from a selection of cells in the 3D view. Polygons can be exported to file. A polygon cell filter can now be configured to use a polyline to define intersected cells in addition to a closed polygon. Performance Tools and Improvements When working with multiple large grid models, it is possible to run into low memory issues. The memory consumption of ResInsight can be monitored using the new Memory Report Dialog . This will display the consumed memory for all cases in the project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2024.03.1</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2024_03_1/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2024_03_1/index.html</guid>
      <description>Bugs fixed See Release Notes 2024.03.1&#xA;See Release Notes on GitHub for further details and information.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2023.12</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_12/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_12/index.html</guid>
      <description>Grid Calculations Grid Property Calculations can now be applied to multiple grid cases. A grid calculation can be used as data source for Grid Case Statistics. The data source for statistics computations can either be a cell property or a grid calculation expression. Time step selection is added to the Grid Case Statistics settings to reduce computation demand. Expressions can be stored to a file and loaded from a file. This makes it possible to reuse expressions in multiple projects. Aggregated Grid Calculations When using a aggregation expression like sum the resulting value will be available as a cell result (the single value is duplicated and displayed for all cells used in the calculation). If the calculation is applied to multiple grids, the aggregated value for each realization will be displayed in the Messages dialog. For each time step, the statistical values are also computed and displayed as text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2023.10</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_10/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_10/index.html</guid>
      <description>Seismic View When working with seismic data, it is no longer required to have a grid model open. Import a seismic cube and surfaces, add some well paths and interact with seismic data.&#xA;Seismic View&#xA;Seismic Data&#xA;Seismic Sections&#xA;Summary Cross Plot Curves Summary Cross Plot curves are now easily available as part of a summary plot. Cross plot of ensemble curves is now supported, and Regression Curves can be created on both single cross plot curves and ensemble statistics curves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2023.06</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_06/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_06/index.html</guid>
      <description>Seismic Data ResInsight supports the following seismic file formats:&#xA;SEGY: file format developed by the Society of Exploration Geophysicists for storing geophysical data VDS: file format for fast random access to multi-dimensional volumetric data as supported by OSDU OpenVDS ZGY: file format for fast random access to multi-dimensional volumetric data as supported by OSDU OpenZGY Seismic Data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2023.03</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_03/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_03/index.html</guid>
      <description>Calculator Improvements A calculated summary vector is now by default available for all wells, all cases and all ensembles.&#xA;[Summary Calculator] [Calculator Expressions] [Grid Calculator]&#xA;Radial Grids Import of radial grids including local grid refinement(LGR) are now supported. Using I and J range filters will filter the grid case based on angle and radius (Theta and R).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in 2023.01</title>
      <link>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_01/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://resinsight.org/releases/release-notes/releasenotes_2023_01/index.html</guid>
      <description>Summary Plotting Summary Plotting is updated with new features and improved workflows:&#xA;Improved logarithmic legend and default ranges Visual appearance of curves is now stable when doing Source Stepping Curve name and plot name improvements Change Data Source by Clicking in 3D The data source for multiple plots can be updated by clicking on a well path in 3D. This feature can be useful for large fields with many wells and you want to investigate a small subset of wells.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>